One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Millet Dumplings
Kibi Dango
Kaido!
Kaido!
This one's gonna end it, Kaido!
Şimdi bitiriyorum işini, Kaido!
Not now!
Hass!
Straw Hat?!
Hasır Şapka?!
When did you get hit?!
Ne ara darbe aldın?
That's not what happened.
Darbe aldığından değil.
It's a side effect of that wrecking ball technique!
O demir topumsu tekniğin yan etkisi.
He won't be able to use haki for about ten minutes!
10 dakika kadar haki kullanamayacak.
Makes sense. All that power comes at a cost.
Anlıyorum. Riskli bir güç demek.
Still, if all of those punches actually hurt him,
Ama saldırıları etkili olduysa...
now's our chance to finish the job!
o iti öldürme fırsatımız olabilir!
Don't push your luck!
Havalara girmeyin!
Luffy! You're dead if you don't get moving!
Luffy, kımıldamazsan öleceksin!
What's that? Already tapped out?
Ne o, bitap mı düştü?
That was quite the tantrum!
İyi coştun ama.
But now, it's lights out for you!
Artık şu işi bitirelim.
Happy Mother's...
Ananın...
Blaze!
Ateşi!
Now hand over Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka'yı ver bana.
Countershock!
Karşı Şok!
Luffy! Wake up!
Luffy, gözlerini aç!
Let's keep up the pressure on Kaido, Killer!
Kaido'yu boş bırakmayalım, Killer!
Okay!
Tamamdır!
Killer! Watch out!
Killer, dikkat et!
The wind that blows heavenward...
Göğe değen rüzgâr,
destroys all in its wake...
yoluna çıkanı yok eder.
Dragon Twister!
Ejder Kasırgası!
Killer!
Killer!
You've got to be kidding!
Kafa mı buluyorsun?
It's like a natural disaster!
Bildiğin doğal afet bu!
Zoro...! Thanks...
Zoro, sağ ol.
Yeah.
Ne demek.
Luffy!
Luffy!
Hold it!
Hop, ağır ol!
You don't get to eat our captain, you son of a bitch!
Kaptanımı yemesene lan şerefsiz!
I see!
Anlıyorum.
That strange haki is coming from his sword!
O garip haki şu kılıçtan geliyor.
Three-Sword Style:
Üç Kılıç Stili:
Black Rope Great Dragon Twister!
Siyah Kement: Büyük Ejder Kasırgası!
He sliced through his scales!
Pullarını kesti!
That punk! He cut Kaido!
O velet, Kaido'yu kesti.
Oh, you got me good!
Of, canım yandı.
I see...
Şimdi anladım.
Just as I thought, that sword...
Demek o elindeki...
belonged to Oden, didn't it?
Oden'in kılıcı ha?
You dare to challenge my own Dragon Twister...
Ejder Kasırgası'nı benimkiyle kapıştırıyor.
I'll put you in your place!
Had bilmez.
Hey! Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh, Zoro...?
Sen misin Zoro?
Something big is coming!
Dev saldırıya dikkat!
Dragon Twister...
Ejder Kasırgası'nın...
Demolition Gust!
Yıkım Rüzgârı!
What a pain...
İşe bak.
First, our supplier dies,
Tedarikçimiz öldü.
then the banquet that we're invited to turns into a battlefield.
Davet edildiğimiz ziyafet de savaş meydanına döndü.
Cipher Pol Aigis 0 World's Most Powerful Intelligence Agency
Dünyanın En Güçlü İstihbarat Servisi, Cipher Pol Aigis 0
Apparently, this battle is to avenge a man who was killed in Wano twenty years ago.
Duyduğuma göre savaşın sebebi 20 yıl önce ölen birinin öcünü almakmış.
Yeah...
Evet...
But when Doflamingo fell from power,
Fakat Doflamingo devrildiğinde...
this clash between Kaido and the Worst Generation became inevitable.
Kaido'yla En Kötü Nesil'in savaşı kaçınılmaz olmuştu.
It was fate...
Kaderin cilvesine bak.
that brought the samurai and the pirates together.
Samuraylar korsanlarla iş tutuyor.
With the world order hanging on a knife's edge...
Dünya dengelerinin değişeceği bir noktadayız.
Imagine if both of those Emperors were to somehow fall...
Olur da iki Yonko devrilirse...
There's no telling what would happen to the world.
Neler olacağını kestirmek güç.
But we needn't worry about that.
Fakat endişeye mahal yok.
The enemy invaders...
Adaya saldıran düşmanın sayısı...
number 5,400.
5.400.
But 400 have fallen.
Şimdiden 400'ünün işi bitti.
On the other hand,
Öte yandan,
we Beast Pirates...
biz Canavar Korsanları'nın...
number 30,000.
30 bini aşkın adamı var.
But 3,000 of them have already fallen.
Şimdiden 3 bininin işi bitti.
The samurai have done well.
Aferin samuraylara.
The difference in numbers is so vast that a direct attack would never reach the leader.
Aradaki güç farkından ötürü, doğrudan saldırmış olsalardı lidere ulaşamazlardı.
Their infiltration plan has worked out brilliantly.
Yaptıkları içeri sızma planı zekiceydi.
But in this battle, simply taking the leader's head won't cut it.
Ancak, liderin kellesini alsalar bile bu savaş sona ermeyecek.
(27000)
(27000)
This is an all-out war. There's no refuge on the island.
Bu adadan kaçış yok. Topyekûn bir savaş bu.
If Kaido's top officers are left unchecked...
Kaido'nun kudretli komutanları sahaya inerse...
each will easily eliminate 100 soldiers at a time.
her biri rahatlıkla 100 adamı indirir.
If this new generation can't stop the top officers...
En Kötü Nesil onların hakkından gelemezse...
...this game of go will end with all black pieces on the board.
oyun tahtasındaki tüm taşlar siyaha döner.
The outcome of this battle has already been decided.
Hangi tarafın kazanacağı bariz gibi duruyor.
Crush one another as much as you want...
İndirebildiğiniz kadar indirin...
my dear pirates.
korsan ahalisi.
Why does he look like that?
Bu görünüş de ne?
Is that his hybrid form?
Yarı insan hâli mi bu?
Hey, Linlin!
Hey, Linlin!
Isn't this fun?
Çok keyif alıyorum!
You took the words right out of my mouth!
Ben de az keyif almıyorum.
Kaido!
Kaido!
Listen up, fellas!
Kulağınızı dört açın!
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Headliner Speed Horse Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Speed At Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
To break this deadlock,
Bu tehlikeyi bertaraf etmek için Queen-sama bana harika bir şey verdi.
Looking hot as ever, Madam Speed!
Yine etrafa güzellik saçıyorsunuz, Speed-sama!
So, where is this "secret weapon"?
Peki o şey nerede?
Right here.
İşte.
It'll dramatically boost your body's healing,
Bunu bir yediniz mi...
and improve muscle strength...
iyileşme hızınız da kas gücünüz de...
significantly!
tavan yapar!
What?!
Ne?
Are you for real?!
Ciddi misiniz?
That said...
Yalnız...
it looks really delicious...
çok leziz görünüyor.
Give me that dumpling immediately!
O dangoyu yemek istiyorum!
Headliner Briscola Gorilla Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Briscola Goril Gülücük Meyvesi Kullanıcısı Canavar Korsanları Üyesi
Looks like you got pretty roughed up, Briscola.
Bakıyorum da haşatın çıkmış, Briscola.
Shut up!
Kes!
If I don't get my revenge against those annoying, shitty Straw Hats,
Eğer ki o yavşak Hasır Şapkalar'dan intikamımı alamazsam...
I'll never be satisfied!
gözüm açık giderim!
I'll let you have one, then.
Al ye o zaman.
Just one bite will flip your world upside down.
Bir tane yediğinde hayatın değişecek.
Here.
Yakala.
How is it, Briscola?
Nasıl Briscola-sama?
Feels like it's working...
İşe yarıyor mu desem,
Or maybe not...
yaramıyor mu desem...
No way.
Mümkün değil.
Huh?
Heh?
You fool...
Sen gelip de...
You're not trying to say that Queen's homemade dumpling...
Queen-sama'nın hazırladığı bu dangoya...
is a failure, are you?
olmamış demiyorsun ya?
Gulp!
Hık!
Boing!
Zıp!
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Zıp! Zıp! Zıp!
Wee!
Fiyu!
It's amazing!
Süper bir şeymiş!
I feel pure power coursing through my veins!
Güçle dolup taşıyorum!
That's awesome!
Muhteşem!
I want one too, Boss Briscola!
- Kıskandım sizi Briscola-sama!
Madam Speed! Might I have a dumpling too?
Speed-sama, ben de bir tane rica edebilir miyim?
I want one too!
Ben de!
– Two for us!
– Biz de!
Of course!
Tabii ki!
I've got enough here for every last Gifter!
Yetenekliler'in hepsine yetecek kadar var.
– Yay!
– Oley!
– Delicious!
– Çok iyi!
Once you finish eating, get ready to fight!
Yiyen savaşa hazırlansın!
There's no time to waste!
Boşa vakit harcamayın!
The Straw Hats won't wait for us!
Hasır Şapkalar bizi beklemez.
Horsella!
Kısrak-chan!
I wanna go to Onigashima, too!
Ben de Onigashima'ya gitmek istiyorum!
No one let me go with them...
Kimse onlarla gitmeme izin vermedi...
So...
O yüzden...
Leave it to me, Master!
Bu işi bana bırakın efendim!
Millet Dumpling!
Kibi Dango!
Every one of these brings us another ally!
Her dangoda müttefik sayımız bir artar.
Millet Dumpling...
Kibi Dango...
Millet Dumpling!
Kibi Dango!
Millet Dump–
Kibi Dan–
Master, I think you'd better stop now...
Efendim, artık dursanız iyi olur.
I'm okay...
Ben iyiyim.
There's no way I can bring Kaido down all by myself...
Kaido'yu deviremem belki...
So...
ama...
I have to do whatever I can to help!
yapabileceğim tek şey olan bunu yapabilirim.
I want a Wano without Orochi and Kaido, with Momo as the shogun!
Orochi'yle Kaido'dan arınmış ve Momo'nun başa geçtiği Wano'yu...
That's the future I want to see!
görmek istiyorum!
And I'm tired of being hungry all the time...
Ayrıca artık midemin guruldamasını istemiyorum.
I wanna eat...
Yemek yemek istiyorum.
I understand.
Anladım.
Let's fight!
Dövüşelim!
Yeah, let's do it!
Evet, yapalım gitsin!
Let's have something to eat first, and then we'll lie in wait for our chance to strike!
Yemek yiyelim de önce. Sonra saklanıp fırsat kollarız.
– Okay! – All right!
– Tamam! – Pekâlâ!
Ready...
Hazır...
Start!
Başla!
Eat this!
Ye!
Huh?! It's delicious!
Heh?! Bayıldım!
– Delicious!
– Enfes!
Eat this!
Ye!
Delicious!
Harika!
Eat up, Gifters!
Hadi yiyin bakalım Yetenekliler!
Look! It's the vice warden from Udon, Daifugo!
Bakın, Udon'un müdür yardımcısı, Daifugo bu!
Take him down!
İndirin!
You put us through hell!
Bize o kadar işkence ettin!
Sorry about that, guys! Let's just put it aside for a bit!
Kusura bakmayın. Şimdilik bunu unutalım.
What?!
Ne?!
– Oh, Daifugo, sir! Thank you for your hard work!
– Daifugo-sama! Emekleriniz için teşekkürler!
No time for pleasantries!
Nezakete lüzum yok!
Eat this!
Şunu ye!
Eat this! Serve the master!
Şunu ye ve efendimin hizmetkârı ol!
General Left!
General'in Solu!
We're not done yet!
Daha bitmedi!
Sasaki, sir!
Sasaki-sama!
This is it!
Bitirme vakti.
General–
General–
Hold him down!
Tutun şunu!
Hey, come on!
Hey, adiler!
Outta the way, you bums!
Bi' çekilin gidin lan!
You may be strong, but even you can't shake off this many of us!
Hayvan gibi güçlü olsan da bu kadarımızı üstünden atamazsın.
Didn't you know? We Gifters have been given special abilities!
Ne de olsa biz, özel güçler verilmiş Yetenekliler'iz.
We're no ordinary soldiers!
Normal asker değiliz!
These are some real tough customers...
Fena güçlüler!
– Franky!
– Franky!
That must be...
Bu ses...
Usopp! Nami! And Otama!
Usopp ve Nami! Otama da mı?
Wha... why?!
O ne alaka?
Wait, this is no time for questions!
Şimdi bu sorunun sırası değil!
Good timing! Help me get these guys off of–
Şükürler olsun. Şunlardan kurtulmama–
– Help!
– Yardım et!
They're being chased by everyone and their mother!
Peşlerinde düşman sürüsü var!
For crying out loud! Things just went from bad to worse!
Durumum daha da kötüleşti!
Gifters! Push ahead and block the way!
Yetenekliler mi? Aynen öyle devam edin!
When it comes to numbers, we have the advantage!
Sayı söz konusu olduğunda avantaj bizde!
They can't win unless the tide turns all over the island!
Adadaki güçlerimiz azalmadığı sürece kazanma şansları yok!
What am I supposed to do?!
Ne yapacağım?!
I...
Bu yüzden...
I'm here to turn that tide!
şartları eşitlemek için geldim!
Everyone, please!
Millet lütfen!
Franosuke needs you!
Franosuke'ye...
Help him!
yardım edin!
– Got it, Master!
– Emredersiniz efendim!
What?!
Ne?!
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
Whew! That was close!
Oh be! Ucuz atlattım.
Great work, guys!
Harikasınız çocuklar!
What the hell are you dolts thinking?!
N'apıyorsunuz ulan siz?
Sasaki!
Sasaki!
Page One! Ulti!
Page One! Ulti!
They've switched sides! Trample them all!
Taraf değiştirdi onlar! Alayını ez gitsin!
Switched sides?!
Taraf mı değiştirdiler?
What could they possibly gain by siding with the samurai?
Samurayların yanında yer alarak ne elde edecekler ki?
It's probably one of their abilities!
Muhtemelen onların yeteneklerinden biri.
Isn't that right?!
Öyle değil mi?
You really are asking for a crushed skull this time!
Bu sefer pekmezini akıtacağım!
Not again!
İstemez, kalsın!
Lightning alert!
Yıldırım uyarısı!
This one's a real heart-stopper, so look alive!
Dikkat et, kalp krizi geçirebilirsin!
Thunder Lance...
Gök Gürültüsü Mızrağı...
Tempo!
Tempo!
Big Sis!
Abla!
Damn! That hurts!
Hay, çok canım yandı.
She's done it now! That rotten bitch!
O kevaşe şimdi çizgiyi aştı!
I knew that wouldn't be enough... I need more powerful lightning!
Yeterli olmayacağını biliyordum. Daha güçlü bir yıldırımla vurmalıyım.
She used some weird trick!
Acayip bir numara kullanıyor!
Guys! Take them down!
İndirin şunları!
They'll only get in our way if we leave them be!
Onları boş bırakırsak başımıza iş açarlar!
– Aye, aye, Sasaki!
– Başüstüne, Sasaki-sama!
Not on my watch!
Rüyanızda görürsünüz!
Lethal...
Ölümcül...
Millet Dumpling Star!
Dango Yıldızı!
What was that?
Bu neydi?
Everybody!
Millet!
Follow me!
Beni takip edin!
– Aye, aye, Master!
– Emredersiniz efendim!
Huh?!
Heh?!
What?! Hey! What's going on?!
Ne?! Hey! N'oluyor lan?
Wait, Armored Division!
Bekleyin, Zırhlı Birlik!
Whoa there.
Hey hey.
You oughta stay focused.
Dikkatini versene.
Did you forget...
Kiminle kapıştığını...
who you're fighting?
unuttun mu?!
Franken-Sword...
Frankılıç...
V-for-Victory Flash!
Zaferin V Işıltısı!
Damn...
Hay...
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Bu ne be?
Be a good boy.
Uslu dur,
Black Leg Sanji.
Kara Bacak Sanji.
Banquet Hall Third Floor
Üçüncü Kattaki Ziyafet Salonu
My goodness...
Cidden...
Such a cute boy, acting out like this.
Yaramazlık yapman çok şeker.
So much power, but what a shame...
Güçlüsün bir de, yazık.
You beat the hell out of the men,
Erkekleri komalık etmene rağmen...
but you can't even lay a finger on the women.
kadınlara bir fiske dahi vurmadın.
It seems your chances of victory have dropped to zero.
Kazanma şansın yok.
Your life is in the palm of my hand.
Artık hayatın ellerimde.
Now then, it's time for you to call out...
Hadi durma,
for Nico Robin!
Nico Robin'i çağır!
This is Caiman Lady.
Bu kızın adı Caiman Lady.
If you speak loudly to this woman...
Ona doğru konuşursan...
your voice will be heard all over the castle.
sesin tüm kalede duyulur.
After that, I'll set you free.
Sonra seni serbest bırakacağım.
Those were Kaido's orders.
Kaido-san'ın emri böyle.
What are you gonna do to Robin?
Robin'e ne yapacaksınız?
Let's see...
Bakalım...
We'll gang up on her, capture her...
Her yönden saldırıp onu yakalayacak...
and maim her limbs until she's paralyzed.
ve hareket edemesin diye sakatlayacağız.
Only once we're "finished" with her, which could take years and years,
Onunla işimiz bitene kadar,
will we finally kill her.
öldürmeyeceğiz.
So don't you worry.
Yani merak etme.
Damn you...
Kahrolası...
Don't underestimate Nico Robin!
Nico Robin'i hafife alma!
Detected! Detected!
Buldum! Buldum!
Performance Floor
Gösteri Katı
Red Scabbard samurai, detected!
Kızıl Kınlar'ı buldum!
It seems they've escaped the rooftop battle!
Çatıdaki savaştan kaçmış gibi duruyorlar!
Bloodied and beaten!
Oluk oluk kanları akıyor!
But still breathing, it seems!
Yine de hâlâ yaşıyorlar.
Location... behind the castle tower!
Kale kulesinin arkasındaki...
The second floor of the treasury at the second bailey!
ikinci katta bulunan hazine odasındalar!
They must've escaped from Kaido.
Kaido-san'dan kaçmışlar demek.
I've got my hands full over here.
Şu an işim var.
Can someone else handle it?
Halledebilecek biri yok mu?
Go to the treasury right away and kill all the samurai!
Biri derhal hazine odasına gidip samurayların işini bitirsin!
Did you get all of that, Madame Black Maria?
Duydunuz mu, Black Maria-sama?
Yes, King...
Evet, King...
I'll go.
ben giderim.
This floor is connected to the second floor of the treasury.
Bu kat direkt hazine odasının ikinci katına çıkıyor!
Want me to finish the Red Scabbards off?
Kızıl Kınlar'ın işini bitirsem yeter öyle değil mi?
Yeah, thanks!
Evet, sağ ol.
Kin'emon... They all lost?!
Kin'emon... Yenilmişler mi?!
Wait! Don't go!
Bekle, gitme!
But be careful! There are ten people...
Ama dikkatli ol. Odada 10 kişi...
in that room!
saydım!
It's hard to make out in the darkness,
İçerisi karanlık olduğundan net göremiyorum ama...
but someone is trying to help the samurai!
birisi samurayların yaralarına bakıyor!
Hurry up and kill them!
Hemen onları öldür!
Someone's...
Orada...
in there!
birisi var!